The anger. The destructiveness. The urge to kill in
cold blood. They weren't born with it...
The Boys Next Door is a crime, drama, thriller
film directed by Penelope Spheeris.
Roy and Bo leave their small town the weekend after
graduation for a short road trip to LA.
Soon, they find themselves lashing out and
leaving a trail of bodies behind them.
The violence escalates throughout.
Roy Alston, played by Maxwell Caulfield.
Bo Richards, played by Charlie Sheen.
Angie, played by Patti D'Arbanville.
Detective Mark Woods, played by Christopher McDonald.
Nancy, played by Moon Unit Zappa.
Detective Ed Hanley, played by Hank Garrett.
The Boys Next Door (released as No Apparent Motive in Australia) is a 1985 American neo-noir crime
drama film directed by Penelope Spheeris, from a screenplay by Glen Morgan and James Wong.
It stars Maxwell Caulfield and Charlie Sheen as two sociopathic teenagers who leave their small town
home on the day of their high school graduation and embark on a crime and murder spree.
The film was Spheeris' second narrative feature following Suburbia (1984),
and was released by New World Pictures on November 1, 1985.
The film explores themes of gun, holiday, murder, arcade, serial killer.
The tone is intense and dark and emotional.